To build a predictive model,
要构建预测模型
you first start with a bunch of data where the outcome is already known.
你先从一些已经知道结果的数据开始
This data is called the training set.
此数据称为训练集
The training set will have several variables,
训练集有几个变量
called predictor variables, as well as the outcome or target variable.
称为预测变量 以及结果变量或目标变量
For example, if you want to predict the likelihood that a student
例如 如果要预测学生的可能性
will graduate based on some information you have about them,
会根据你对他们的一些信息毕业
you train your model using historical data on
使用历史数据对模型进行训练
students for whom you already know whether or not they graduated.
你已经知道他们毕业的学生了
The training dataset helps the model understand
培训数据集有助于模型理解
the relationship between predictor variables and the outcome or target variable.
预测变量与结果或目标变量之间的关系
The model is then applied to a new dataset where the outcomes are not yet known.
然后 模型将应用于尚未知道结果的新数据集
We call this dataset the Test dataset.
我们将此数据集称为测试数据集
In the students example,
在学生中
the test data would be new or existing
测试数据将是新的或现有
students for whom we have the predictor variable data,
我们有预测变量数据的学生
but the graduation outcome is not yet known.
但毕业的结果还不清楚
You apply the model to that dataset to get
将模型应用于该数据集以获取
an estimate of the likelihood each student will graduate.
估计每个学生毕业的可能性
The more training data you have,
你的训练数据越多
the more accurately the model can predict outcomes.
模型可以更精确地预测结果
In this first project,
在这个项目中
you'll use a predictive model designed to predict
你会用一个预测模型来预测
the price of diamonds based on their various attributtes.
钻石的价格
The model has already been trained using
模型已使用
a large dataset of diamonds where the prices are already known.
已经知道价格的钻石大数据集
You'll be using the results of the model to predict prices for
您将使用模型的结果来预测价格
another set of diamonds for which you will have their attributes,
你将拥有的另一组钻石
but the price is not known. Good luck.
但价格是不知道的 祝你好运